[EP06]
Who dares to do this?
My lover,
let me ask you,
what do you do
in my courtyard?
He feeds the tanuki.
You keep him and the tanuki in the backyard,
and summon him at any time.
I've seen it many times.
Huh?
Why didn't I know
I fed cats?
I knew you wouldn't admit it.
Guards,
bring the cats here.
See,
the cats are so close to you.
They must be yours.
Do you remember
how I became your wife?
Because...
Because you are a wild cat.
Right.
Because Ling Shenxing
saved me from a group of crazy cats.
But since then,
I've been allergic to cat hair.
I can't touch cats.
Madam.
Cousin.
I don't think
she would lie about this.
She said
she's allergic to cat hair.
That's not enough to prove anything.
It's just her word.
Besides,
Mammy also said
she has a butterfly birthmark.
That's a fact.
Your Ladyship,
Young Madam does have a birthmark.
But Miss Ye...
Is Young Madam's birthmark
a butterfly birthmark?
Young Madam,
please change your clothes.
It's not decent
to meet people in wet clothes.
Yes.
Put it down.
My lower body isn't wet.
I just need to change the upper part.
Yes.
[So it's to]
[see my birthmark]
[while I'm changing clothes.]
The birthmark on her waist is blunt.
You're lying.
I saw it clearly.
There is a butterfly nevus
on her lower back.
Madam,
Young Madam must have
bought off the nanny.
Ridiculous.
The aide-de-camp was on guard at the door
when the examination was conducted.
What do you think this is, a brothel?
You're just using the butterfly nevus
on my body as an excuse.
Fortunately, I covered it with a blunt nevus.
As for you,
you took double pay last month
and gave it to the Ye Family's Renhe Pawnshop.
What treasure did you redeem?
Why are you looking at me?
You did such a thing
to reverse the black and white.
Think about your family's safety.
Young Marshal,
Please let me go.
You were so arrogant just now.
Now you're begging for mercy.
You should be begging the Young Madam.
You damaged her reputation.
Her will
is my will.
Xing.
Grandma.
The family fears nothing more than harboring evildoers.
You decide.
You are the kindest.
Please spare me.
Spare me.
I remember
you just said
I'm the wildest
and the most unreasonable.
It's all rumors.
Drown her.
You Lings
love drowning people.
I'll send you to the bottom
to check it out.
No!
You vicious woman,
you'll die a miserable death!
You...
It's none of my business.
Young Madam, help!
Cousin,
the Lings have always been kind to servants.
This punishment is too...
She's Madam Ling.
She has the final say
in the backyard.
Cui Lan and that man
wouldn't dare frame me alone.
There's
a mastermind behind this.
The show isn't over yet.
I remember seeing a jade pendant
on her ear.
It's the same style
as the new Nanyang goods at the Paramount.
If I'm not mistaken,
the owner of the Paramount
seems to be surnamed Ye.
Madam,
this whole thing
is my fault.
I was so focused on protecting the Ling family's reputation
that I believed her lies.
Sister,
I'm sorry.
I misunderstood you.
Amitabha.
You've realized your mistake
and corrected it.
You did it all
for the Ling family.
I don't blame you.
I'm the victim.
I haven't forgiven her.
You just forgive her for me.
Young Madam.
How can you talk to an elder like this?
If you weren't so flirtatious,
how could this have happened?
Her mistake is because of my behavior.
What a victim blaming.
Since her mistake is because of my behavior,
my behavior
because of you?
A crooked roof will have crooked walls.
How dare you!
Are you okay, Madam?
[The faint bitterness]
[is the same as the one in my medicine.]
Calm down.
[Could it be]
[that one of them]
[poisoned me?]
Put this woman
in the pig cage in the backyard.
[Does this mean]
[he wants me to leave first?]
Brother,
are we not a family after getting married?
Are we not a family after getting married?
Of course, we are.
We'll always be a family.
I'll protect you for a lifetime.
Yes.
Why does he look like my brother?
Wan'er,
I'll be with you.
I'll always be with you.
Let me go.
Who is this?
Xiao Wan'er,
long time no see.
Just like the first time we met,
you ran into my arms again.
Who are you?
[It seems that she has lost her memory.]
Let me introduce myself.
Chu Nanfeng,
the man you love the most.
Is he crazy?
Come with me.
Stop.
Wan'er is going back to the Su Family with me.
The Su Family?
There is no
Su Family in Yang City now.
Let go of me!
Ouch.
Are you okay?
Su Hong,
whether it's the Su family or the Chu family,
it's better than staying in the Ling family.
Stop!
Who dares to take away my woman?
You're hurting me.
Ling Shenxing,
the one who's not loved is the third wheel.
You know we love each other.
Who loves you?
Why force me?
My God.
I'm so popular.
They won't shoot, will they?
Don't hurt me.
Wan,
choose me
or him?
Su Muwan's marriage
was requested by the Su family.
She lives and dies a Ling.
She has no choice.
Don't do this.
It hurts.
Wan,
leave the Ling family first.
Want the truth? Come with me.
Don't be impulsive.
Everything of the Su family,
including my life,
can be yours as long as you don't hurt Wan'er.
Get out of here!
It's not your turn to speak.
The Sus...
Is there still a Su family in Yang City?
I'm still here.
As long as I'm still here,
you can't hurt Wan'er.
Throw him out.
Go and investigate everything about Su Muwan,
the Young Madam.
The more detailed, the better.
And
bring back my wife.